{
    "id": "yutoohashi",
    "name": "Yuto Ohashi",
    "yomi": "オオハシユウト",
    "text": [
        "1994。ひとりとか風景とかそういうことについて。",
        "about something like being alone and a scenery."
    ],
    "link": [
        {
            "a": "Website",
            "href": "http://yutoohashi.net/"
        }
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "Q1",
            "question": "Is there a boundary?",
            "jp": "境い目はあるとおもう",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "いいえ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q2",
            "question": "Which prefer if you keep walking?",
            "jp": "歩き続けるならどちらがいい",
            "yes": "in the city",
            "left": "街",
            "no": "in a harbor",
            "right": "港"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q3",
            "question": "In the darkest place you would",
            "jp": "もっとも暗い場所で",
            "yes": "lay down",
            "left": "横たわる",
            "no": "close your eyes",
            "right": "目を瞑る"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q4",
            "question": "Do you know where it came from?",
            "jp": "どこから来たのかを知っている",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "No i don't",
            "right": "いいえ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q5",
            "question": "Can you sleep in the lighted place?",
            "jp": "明るい場所で眠ることができる",
            "yes": "Yes i can",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "No i can't",
            "right": "いいえ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q6",
            "question": "Which do you need?",
            "jp": "聴診器と時計、どちらが必要だと思う",
            "yes": "a stethoscope",
            "left": "聴診器",
            "no": "a watch",
            "right": "時計"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q7",
            "question": "Do you think there is a better place?",
            "jp": "今よりももっといい場所があるとおもう",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "No i don't",
            "right": "いいえ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q8",
            "question": "When you open your eyes you will see",
            "jp": "目を開くと",
            "yes": "the sky",
            "left": "空がみえる",
            "no": "some people",
            "right": "人がみえる"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q9",
            "question": "Do you think it is okay if you have a day you do nothing?",
            "jp": "なにもしない日があってもいいと思う",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "いいえ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q10",
            "question": "When you say thank you you feel",
            "jp": "ありがとうと伝えるとき",
            "yes": "embarrassed",
            "left": "照れくさい",
            "no": "happy",
            "right": "嬉しくなる"
        }
    ]
}